<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinCal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_calculations">Calculations</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="rupee">\u20B9</string>
    <string name="emdash"> — </string>
    <string name="emi_description">An equated monthly installment (EMI) is a fixed payment amount made by a borrower to a lender at a specified date each calendar month. Equated monthly installments are used to pay off both interest and principal each month so that over a specified number of years, the loan is paid off in full.</string>
    <string name="fd_description">A fixed deposit (FD) is a financial instrument provided by banks or NBFCs which provides investors with a higher rate of interest than a regular savings account, until the given maturity date. It may or may not require the creation of a separate account.</string>
    <string name="rd_description">Recurring Deposit is a special kind of Term Deposit offered by banks in India which help people with regular incomes to deposit a fixed amount every month into their Recurring Deposit account and earn interest at the rate applicable to Fixed Deposits. Minimum Period of RD is 6 months and maximum is 10 years.</string>
    <string name="sip_description">A SIP is a flexible and easy investment plan. Your money is auto-debited from your bank account and invested into a specific mutual fund scheme.You are allocated certain number of units based on the ongoing market rate (called NAV or net asset value) for the day.</string>
    <string name="fixed_deposit_tip">Fixed deposits are prone to uncertainty because interest rates tend to move in multi-year cycles. To avoid this, build a ladder of FDs which have different tenures. If you have 4 lakh to invest, split the amount in four deposits of 1 lakh each for one, two, three and four years. When the 1-year deposit matures , reinvest the maturity proceeds in the 4-year FD. By doing so, the highs and lows in interest rates will balance out over a period of time.</string>
    <string name="rd_tips">Recurring deposits are useful for small short-term goals over horizon of 1-3 years, but returns from these deposits are taxable. Hence, the actual profit is lower than calculated. </string>
    <string name="sip_tips">As an old saying that “A Goal Without Plan Is Just A Wish”, so your every investment plan should be backed by the Goal. The goals could be of short-term like going on vacation, buying a car etc. or long-term such as children education, children marriage, retirement etc. Selection of mutual funds must be based on this and every mutual fund SIP should be linked to one financial goal.</string>
    <string name="rp_tips"> Save A High Proportion Of Your Income. The key to retiring early is to start saving early, and to save a high proportion of your income. If you are able to save 15% of your income from age 20 onwards, retirement at 55 should be a relatively easy goal. If you start later, the amount you have to save increases.</string>
    <string name="fd_stats_warning">Bank interest rate for Fixed Deposit changes with tenure and breaking FD before its maturity date attracts penalty (reduced interest) which varies with bank, hence yearly or monthly break up is not provided</string>

    <!-- Quotes Array -->
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item> Beware of little expenses. A small leak will sink a great ship. </item>
        <item> Your net worth to the world is usually determined by what remains after your bad habits are subtracted from your good ones. </item>
        <item> The way to become rich is to put all your eggs in one basket and then watch that basket. </item>
        <item> Watch your finances like a hawk.</item>
        <item> A wise person should have money in their head, but not in their heart.</item>
        <item> Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune. </item>
        <item> It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor. </item>
        <item> Happiness is not in the mere possession of money; it lies in the joy of achievement, in the thrill of creative effort </item>
        <item> It’s good to have money and the things that money can buy, but it’s good, too, to check up once in a while and make sure that you haven’t lost the things that money can’t buy. </item>
        <item> If all the economists were laid end to end, they’d never reach a conclusion. </item>
        <item> Try to save something while your salary is small; it’s impossible to save after you begin to earn more.  </item>
        <item> Investing should be more like watching paint dry or watching grass grow. If you want excitement, take $800 and go to Las Vegas. </item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Author Array Position Corresponding To Quotes Array -->
    <string-array name="author">
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> Benjamin Franklin </item>
        <item> Andrew Carnegie </item>
        <item> H. Jackson Brown, JR. </item>
        <item> Jonathan Swift </item>
        <item> Jim Rohn </item>
        <item> Seneca </item>
        <item> Franklin D. Roosevelt </item>
        <item> George Lorimer </item>
        <item> George Bernard Shaw </item>
        <item> Jack Benny </item>
        <item> Paul Samuelson </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
